Hyde Park, Boston, Mass. First Congregational Church of Hyde Park records, 1860-2003. RG4923
Congregational Library & Archives
Hyde Park, Boston, Mass. First Congregational Church of Hyde Park records, 1860-2003.
Congregational Library & Archives
First Congregational Church (Hyde Park, Boston, Mass.)
Owen, George W., active 1911-1948
Davis, Perley, B., 1832-1916
RG4923
15.4 Cubic Feet (15 boxes, 6 cases)
The First Church of Hyde Park was established in 1860, incorporated in 1895, and closed in 2009. The original church building was constructed in 1865. Rev. George Owen gave the first sermon in the new church building in 1911 and new stained glass windows were added in 1917. This collection contains administrative records, membership information, photographs and scrapbooks, and church group records from 1860-2003 with the bulk of the records created between 1860-1930.
Restrictions on Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted and open to the public.
Acquisition Information
Materials were donated to the Congregational Library & Archives by First Congregational Church of Hyde Park in April 2009; no accession number.
Historical Note
In June 1857 the first religious meetings were held in the village of Hyde Park and a Sabbath School was started. The first Congregational service in Hyde Park was held in December, in Bragg's Hall and led by Rev. L.R. Eastman. On May 7, 1863, an Ecclesiastical Council met to a organize a Congregational Church and a new church of 10 members was established and named the Hyde Park Congregational Church.
A gift of land was secured from the Real Estate and Building Company in 1865. The church operated as a Church and Society from 1866-1895 when it became incorporated. The original church building was erected in 1868.
Reverend Perley B. Davis was installed as the first pastor of Hyde Park Congregational church in 1867 and remained in the position until 1892. He was proceeded by Reverends Andrew W. Archibald, Henry N. Hoyt, and Lucius F. Reed between 1893-1910. Rev. George W. Owen served as reverend from 1911-1948 and oversaw the church during its largest period of growth and change as it moved into a newly erected church building at the start of his appointment.
The new auditorium seated 520 on the floor and 170 on the balcony. An organ was gifted to the new church by Mr. Edward E. Taylor of Boston in honor of his mother. The new church building had plain glass windows upon its construction. George Owen chose the theme of the evolution of Christianity for new stained-glass windows which were created by Charles J. Connick and installed in 1917. In November 1915 the old church building was sold.
The church continued operating through the 20th century. Due to declining membership the church closed in 2009.
Ministers
1867-1892 Perley B. Davis
1892-1897 Andrew W. Archibald
1898-1908 Henry N. Hoyt
1908-1910 Lucius F. Reed
1911-1948 George W. Owen
1948-1953 Eugene Gilmore
1954-1955 Malcom W. Garland
1956-1960 Allan R. McAllaster
1961-1967 Kenneth J. Sanford
1967-1989 K.S. Jordan
1990-2007 J.M. Smith
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of records from the First Congregational Church of Hyde Park from its inception in 1860 until 2003. Records include administrative records, meeting minutes, financial records, correspondence, bulletins and event programs, building records including blueprints, membership records and materials, photographs and scrapbooks.
The bulk of administrative records and correspondence were created between 1860-1930. The membership records cover the church's entire time frame. Researchers interested in the church's membership should devote time to the membership cards in boxes 13-16.
There is a largely complete collection of church bulletins from 1888-1976. Also of particular note are the scrapbooks and photographs for those interested in the visual history of the church and its impact on its community as represented from newspaper clippings. The Annals of the First Congregational Church of Hyde Park by William Lewis, 1860-1949, contain a detailed sketch of the church's history during the period for which most of the records in this collection pertain.
Arrangement
Materials in this collection have been arranged into five series by the subject of the records they contain: Administration, Services and fellowship, membership and vital statistics, church groups, and photographs and scrapbooks These series are then then further broken down into subseries by topics and then secondarily by chronology. Series 1 has 6 subseries representing administrative topics, Series 2 has 6 subseries divided by topics related to the services and personnel of the church, Series 3 has 6 subseries divided by the type of membership record, Series 4 has 13 subseries representing each of the church groups, and Series 5 contains 2 subseries divided by type of material.
Series 1: Administration, 1860-1993
Subseries 1: Administrative records, 1860-1954
Subseries 2: Financial records, 1867-1993
Subseries 3: Annual reports, 1870-1958
Subseries 4: Prudential Committee records, 1875-1927
Subseries 5: Supply Committee records, 1892-1910
Subseries 6: Executive Committee records, 1869-1955
Series 2: Services and fellowship, 1868-1999
Subseries 1: Correspondence, 1868-1971
Subseries 2: Ecclesiastical council, 1874-1935
Subseries 3: Events and anniversaries, 1876-1999
Subseries 4: Bulletins, 1888-1976
Subseries 5: Ministers and sermons, 1892-1969
Subseries 6: Member discipline, 1899
Series 3: Membership and vital statistics, 1860-2003
Subseries 1: Admissions, 1860-1999
Subseries 2: Dismissions, 1869-1986
Subseries 3: Member records, 1892-1974
Subseries 4: Membership cards, circa 1880-2000
Subseries 5: Baptisms, weddings, and funerals, 1948-2001
Subseries 6: Membership lists, 1863-2003
Subseries 7: Membership materials, 1870-1925
Series 4: Church groups, 1871-1972
Subseries 1: Sunday school, 1871-1972
Subseries 2: Heart and Hand Society, 1877-1884
Subseries 3: Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor, 1884-1909
Subseries 4: Junior Society of Christian Endeavor, 1889-1902
Subseries 5: Auxiliary to the Woman's Board, 1872-1939
Subseries 6: Junior Auxiliary to the Woman's Board, 1894-1903
Subseries 7: Woman's Home Missionary Union, 1885-1929
Subseries 8: Maternal association, 1889-1906
Subseries 9: Social committee, 1900-1924
Subseries 10: Church Aid Society, 1905-1931
Subseries 11: New Church Building committee, 1884-1917
Subseries 12: Woman's Union, 1917-1923
Subseries 13: Fairmont Circle, 1949-1954
Series 5: Scrapbooks and photographs, 1900-2003
Subseries 1: Scrapbooks, 1900-1938
Subseries 2: Photographs, 1908-2003
Bibliography
First Congregational Church of Hyde Park. 100th Anniversary of the First Congregational Church. Hyde Park, Massachusetts, 1963. 17.11.1 H99.9F
Church bulletins.; Church buildings.; Church correspondence.; Church finance.; Church membership.; Church records and registers.; Church societies.; Clergy conferences.; Photographs.; Sunday schools.; Owen, George W., active 1911-1948; First Congregational Church (Hyde Park, Boston, Mass.); Davis, Perley, B., 1832-1916
- Administration, 1860-1993; 45 Folder; 27 Volume
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains administrative and historical records for the church from its inception until 1999. The most complete records fall between the 1880s-1920s.
  - Administrative records, 1860-1954; 9 Folders; 7 Volumes
    This subseries contains administrative records including meeting minutes, reports, ballots, and notices. It also includes documents relating to the founding of the church and its adminsitration like the church manual, by-laws, and the incorporation document. Finally, it includes a historical overview of the church, and a report from the committee on individual cups.
    - By-laws, 1890-1896 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Hyde Park map, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Church manual, 1885 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Incorporation certificate, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Church records book, 1861-1878 (Box 2, Volume 1)
    - Society records and meeting minutes, 1865-1879 (Box 5, Volume 1)
    - Society records and meeting minutes, 1879-1895 (Box 2, Volume 3)
      Separated Materials
      Items were removed from this volume and placed in folder titled Financial records 1869-1891 (B2/F3) for preservation purposes.
    - Corporation records and meeting minutes, 1895-1913 (Box 2, Volume 2)
    - Church records and meeting minutes, 1878-1889 (Box 3, Volume 2)
    - Church records and meeting minutes, 1890-1905 (Box 3, Volume 3)
    - Church records and meeting minutes, 1905-1954 (Box 3, Volume 1)
    - Church records, 1877-1921 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Church records, 1879-1921 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Church records, 1908-1920 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Annual meeting ballots, 1909-1912 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Meeting warrants and notices, 1880-1931 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Individual Cups, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Annals of the First Congregational Church of Hyde Park by William Lewis, 1860-1949 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Financial records, 1867-1993; 10 Folders; 9 Volumes
    This subseries contains financial reports and finance related correspondence from throughout the church's history. It also contains records created by and concerning the treasurer of the church and financial appeals sent to the church's members.
    - Financial ledger, 1867 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Mortgage, deeds, and legal documents, 1867-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Financial records, 1869-1891 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Materials in this folder were removed from Society Records and Meeting Minutes, 1879-1895 (B2/V3) for preservation purposes.
    - Financial reports and correspondence, 1874-1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Pew rents and taxes, 1876-1896 (Box 2, Volume 5)
    - Pew rents and taxes, 1882-1884 (Box 2, Volume 4)
    - Pew rents and taxes, 1883-1884 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Pew rents and taxes, 1884-1896 (Box 2, Volume 6)
    - Church Debt Subscription, 1879-1880 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer records, 1890-1894 (Box 2, Volume 7)
    - Financial records, 1882-1895 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Benevolence reports and correspondence, 1889-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer of society accounting, 1873-1895 (Box 4, Volume 2)
    - Society of treasurer cash record, 1873-1895 (Box 4, Volume 3)
    - Treasurer of society cash, 1877-1895 (Box 4, Volume 1)
    - Cash book of collections`, 1892-1896 (Box 4, Volume 4)
    - Annual financial reports, 1893-1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Financial appeals, 1896-1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Financial records, 1952-1962 (Box 2, Volume 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1870-1958; 19 Folders
    This subseries contains annual reports from a variety of commitees to be presented to the membership at the annual meeting. The majority of the records in this subseries are from the executive and prudential committees
    - Annual Reports, 1870-1893 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1871-1893 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1894-1903 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports, 1894-1904 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1868-1893 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 1899-1904 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports, 1905-1913 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports, 1905-1914 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Annual Reports, 1905-1913 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports, 1907-1925 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Annual Reports, 1914-1940 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Annual Reports, 1914-1927 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Annual Reports, 1914-1935 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Annual Reports, 1926-1937 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Annual Reports, 1938-1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Annual Reports, 1945-1954 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Annual Reports, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Prudential Committee records, 1875-1927; 2 Folders; 3 Volumes
    This subseries contains the records of the Prudential committee which contains correspondence, reports, and meeting minutes regarding the activities of the committee including overseeing the building and its operations.
    - Prudential committee, 1875-1890 (Box 4, Volume 5)
    - Prudential records, 1877-1922 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Prudential committee, 1890-1895 (Box 4, Volume 6)
    - Prudential committee, 1895-1908 (Box 4, Volume 7)
    - Prudential building records, 1908-1927 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Supply Committee records, 1892-1910; 4 Folders; 4 Volumes
    This subseries contains records from the supply committe which was tasked with finding new ministers for the church. The records in this series include correspondence, meeting minutes, and materials about the various ministerial candidates.
    - Supply committee records on Reverend Andrew Archibald, 1892 (Box 7, Volume 1)
    - Supply committee records on Reverend Henry Hoyt, 1897-1898 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Supply committee records on Reverend Henry Hoyt record book, 1897-1898 (Box 7, Volume 2)
    - Supply committee record book on Lucius F. Reed, 1908 (Box 7, Volume 3)
    - Supply committee records on Lucius F. Reed, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Supply committee records on Reverend Henry Hoyt record book, 1897-1898 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Supply committee meeting minutes, 1910 (Box 7, Volume 3)
    - Supply committee, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee records, 1869-1955; 3 Folders; 4 Volumes
    This subseries contains records from the executive committee including reports, correspondence, meeting minutes, and collected record books pertaining to the activities of the committee especially in regards to chuch administration.
    - Executive committee corespondence, 1869-1912 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Executive committee, 1869-1886 (Box 4, Volume 8)
    - Executive committee, 1896-1912 (Box 9, Volume 1)
    - Executive committee, 1912-1936 (Box 9, Volume 2)
    - Executive committee, 1935-1955 (Box 4, Volume 9)
    - Executive committee reports, 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Executive committee, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Services and fellowship, 1868-1999; 31 Folders; 36 Volumes
  This series contains records related to the church's programming, sermons, and people including correspondence, reports, programs, bulletins, and sermons. It contains a very extensive collection of weekly bulletins from 1888-1976 as well as special event bulletins and programs.
  - Correspondence, 1868-1971; 4 Folders
    This subseries contains church correspondence to and between members of the church, its committees, and the general public.
    - Committee reports and correspondence, 1868-1922 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - S.B. Balkam correspondence, 1879-1901 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - General correspondence, 1880-1913 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence from church to members, 1888-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ecclesiastical council, 1874-1935; 6 Folders
    This subseries contains invitations and correspondence to and from the ecclesiastical council.
    - Ecclesiastical council correspondence A-F, 1875-1934 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Ecclesiastical council correspondence G-O, 1874-1927 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Ecclesiastical council correspondence P-S, 1874-1928 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Ecclesiastical council correspondence T-Z, 1875-1935 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Ecclesiastical council invitations, 1893-1903 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Ecclesiastical council invitations, 1904-1907 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Events and anniversaries, 1876-1999; 7 Folders
    This subseries contains records related to events held by and at the church as well as conferences in which the church participated. The majority of this subsseries is made up of event programs. It also includes correspondence and other written materials pertaining to the events.
    - Musical concerts, 1876-1939 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Anniversary programs, 1886-1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Installation programs, 1885-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Event programs, 1891-1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Unions and conferences, 1903-1911 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Men's and women's group programs and events, 1908-1963 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Event written materials, 1912-1947 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins, 1888-1976; 9 Folders; 34 Volumes
    This subseries contains an extensive collection of weekly church bulletins. Most of the bulletins are contained in boudnd volumes though there is a small number of folders containing unbound bulletins. The bulletin collections are largely complete between the years 1888-1903 and 1915-1976 with only a small number of bulletins from the intervening years.
    - Bulletins, 1888-1889 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bulletins, 1890-1896 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bulletins, 1897-1898 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Bulletins, 1898-1899 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Bulletins, 1899-1900 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bulletins, 1900-1901 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Bulletins, 1902-1906 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bulletins, 1907-1914 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 1)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 2)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 3)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 4)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 5)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 6)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 7)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 8)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 9)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 10)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 11)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 12)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 13)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 14)
    - Bulletins, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Volume 15)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 2)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 3)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 4)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 5)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 6)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 7)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 8)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 9)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 10)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 11)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 12)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 13)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 14)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 15)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 16)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 17)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 18)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 19)
    - Bulletins, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Volume 20)
    - Bulletin, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ministers and sermons, 1892-1969; 3 Folders; 2 Volumes
    This subseries contains records related to ministers and their sermons. It includes the record book and correspondence of George Owen. Correpsondence from and to the ministers of the church, a notebook on the event programming of Perley B. Davis's 25th ordination anniversary, and a small number of printed sermons given or collected by ministers of the church.
    - Perley B. Davis 25th ordination anniversary notebook, 1892 (Box 7, Volume 4)
    - Ministerial communications, 1898-1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - George Owen, 1911-1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - George Owen ledger book, 1930 (Box 7, Volume 5)
    - Sermons, 1936-1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Member discipline, 1899; 2 Folders
    This subseries contains records related to the discipline of two members of the church, Charles Vaugn and Amos F. Bartlett. Records include correspondence and reports.
    - Amos F. Bartlett, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Charles Vaughn, 1889 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Membership and vital statistics, 1860-2003; 78 Folders; 6 Volumes
  This series contains membership and church statistical records. This includes member lists, addmission and dismission paperwork from and to the church, records of baptisms, weddings, and funerals, and an extensive collection of individual membership cards.
  - Admissions, 1860-1999; 21 Folders
    This subseries contains admission forms to the church membership and a list of admitted members.
    - Admissions, 1860-1893 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Admissions, 1894 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Admissions, 1895 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Admissions, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Admissions, 1897-1898 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Admissions, 1899-1900 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Admissions, 1901 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Admissions, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Admissions, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Admissions, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Admissions, 1905 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Admissions, 1906-1907 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Admissions: A-E, 1863-1913 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Admissions: F-M, 1863-1913 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Admissions: N-Z, 1863-1913 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Admissions: A-D, 1907-1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Admissions: E-K, 1907-1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Admissions: L-Q, 1907-1969 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Admissions: R-Z, 1907-1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Admission lists, 1929-1942 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Membership applications, 1974-1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Dismissions, 1869-1986; 31 Folders
    This subseries contains forms and records of dismissal both from Hyde Park and from other churches for members seeking admission to Hyde Park.
    - Dismissal requests, 1893-1894 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Dismissal requests, 1957-1986 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Dissmissals, 1869-1871 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Dissmissals, 1872-1874 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Dismissals, 1875-1876 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Dismissals, 1877 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Dismissals, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Dismissals, 1879 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Dismissals, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Dismissals, 1881 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Dismissals, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Dismissals, 1883-1884 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Dismissals, 1885 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Dismissals, 1886 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Dismissals, 1887 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Dismissals, 1888 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Dismissals, 1889 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Dismissals, 1890 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Dismissals, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Dismissals, 1892 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Dismissals, 1893 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Dismissals, 1894 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Dismissions: A-C, 1878-1934 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Dismissions: D-H, 1893-1934 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Dismissions: I-O, 1895-1935 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Dismissions: P-U, 1876-1934 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Dismissions: V-Z, 1907-1934 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Dismissals: D-G, 1938-1974 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Dismissals: H-J, 1935-1971 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Dismissals: K-Q, 1935-1976 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Dismissals, 1936-1974 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Dismissals: S-Z, 1938-1974 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Member records, 1892-1974; 15 Folders
    This subseries contains records about church members. This includes biographies written by the church about individual members, correspondence from members to the church, and obitiuaries.
    - Letters, biographies A-D, 1892-1926 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Letters, biographies E-L, 1910-1926 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Letters, biographies M-Z`, 1910-1924 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Membership biographies A-C, 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Membership biographies D-H, 1929-1934 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Membership biographies I-O, 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Membership biographies P-S, 1930-1934 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Membership biographies S-Z, 1930-1934 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Membership biographies A-D, 1936-1952 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Membership biographies E-H, 1936-1952 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Membership biographies I-O, 1936-1952 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Membership biographies P-Z, 1936-1952 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Membership biographies A-F, 1953-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Membership biographies G-M, 1953-1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Membership biographies N-Z, 1953-1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Membership cards, circa 1880-2000; 5 Box